Okay, what happened, I was, I, okay, come on.
Okay
Okay, I'll drop the link. I just want to talk for a second. Keep talking dumb. Okay. No, I'm not gonna drop the link for you
No, I'll just gonna say why am I in the last camp? Well, it wasn't because Vita spoke Farsi
I spoke Farsi. That was all fun and games is then this guy. Let me know this guy. He starts saying oh
He she's saying and he said some phrase several times that I just don't want to praise my show
It's it's one of those things you get fly for I tried to explain that I can't say the person's name anymore. I'll just call her
We her name is a Rita. Okay, so I know this woman named Rita. Okay
No relation to anybody else in my so this woman named Rita. I try to explain sir. I already made a fence
I was in my life. Is it because I'm for my protection not I'm trying to offend somebody
But you know people all
Some people won't listen
The reason it's like it reminds me it just really does remind me of Alex though. Like, you know, who I can't I love to talk about
you know Alex Alex
actually
He's going insane too. I mean, it's like I guess everyone's going to say but yeah Alex
He thinks I'm Tony now. I mean, it's like it really he thinks
DC Electra is piranha. I mean rabbit holes. It gets deeper and deeper guys. Okay. I mean, okay
I'm talking about Arthur Arthur talking shit. Shut your fucking mouth like he nobody said anything
Terrific all I said was like Alex McQueen wants your fucking
So Rita so Rita be whatever okay, let me say
Now I can say your name now.
I guess I give you permission so they can't say read.
OK.
So beta, I was trying to say it wasn't.
That I believe that you taught you that I know you didn't say it. It was that he was saying it and it's like the algorithm
I mean, I don't know those partners, but no
Arthur
Identities everyone's trying to fuck it up confused me or something just come on here or tell me at least so I know
Who's who I won't mean? I won't give you a yes. Yes. Yes, and and be a by the way, you know Arthur is big Nisha
Okay, your friend
Jeff my now. Oh
Okay, I'll be silent so can't even explain it even when I do
I'm letting you cut that
Then is that I'm better back say she's she left now. She's telling me to shut my mouth. Okay, so
Go ahead. Uh, you know, you know what the only reason we get so upset is because we love each other so much
And that's the only reason we do because we hate each other
We actually didn't like or this didn't fuck with each other. We were just like, oh
Whoever that person they're relevant. We're so relevant to each other that we get all riled up. Okay, right?
I love to make sense
No, you'll tell me shut up. Yeah, don't tell me to shut it. That's like telling it
It's like it's like the gay guy that shut his mouth is like telling a woman it's just offensive
But if you say man, it's like
yeah
Stop saying you're not I'm not gonna mod you. I'm not gonna mod you nor kick you out of the chat
You can say whatever you want in the chat. Go ahead
This this won't say
You know, you know what? Okay, what?
Something is up. Look at me. Now you're telling me to stop on my own channel. I'm just trying to run a channel
I never did any wrong to you guys. I don't understand. You're telling me you're probably
get people
Okay, good
No, you didn't you didn't do nothing site
You
Do we're older? No, no, why why is why is Sam bitch up here? Why is Sam bitch up here?
I don't even know you my nigga. What a fan Ray
No, who you calling a nigger who you calling that whoa?
Struck out
Denison I know
Clumsy you was hanging with beta all night with you fucking weirdos
You could come on join Sykes
Clumsy is a bitch ass nigga, cute complaining.
I'm magic cute complaining about picture.
Nigga, y'all didn't start complaining nigga.
I go live and still cooking nigga.
What happened Papas?
I'm not bad.